Guide to the Fred Friendly Papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series VI: General, 1934-2004
  - Subseries VI.3: Columbia University, 1968-2002
    Friendly's work at Columbia is documented by lecture notes, assignments and exams, and memos to students and faculty, which have been arranged chronologically, and by course syllabi, which are arranged alphabetically by title.
    This subseries also includes notes, clippings, and information booklets relating to the Summer Program in Broadcast and Print Journalism for Members of Minority Groups, which Friendly created and directed. The program's goal to "bring more members of minority groups into journalism" by providing instruction and training was successful; though most students came into the program without any form of training in journalism, thirty-one of the thirty-six members of the first graduating class were hired by major television and radio stations to work as writers or reporters. The program was later renamed the Michele Clark Fellowship Program for Minority Journalists in memory of a Columbia student. These files have been arranged chronologically
    - School of Journalism
      - General, undated (Box 188, Folder F.7)
      - Class Assignments, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 188, Folder F.8-9)
      - NET Journal Special "The Warren Years"--Transcript and Notes, undated (Box 188, Folder F.10)
      - Response to 1968 Riots, 1968 (Box 188, Folder F.11)
      - Memos to Students, 1968-1971 (Box 188, Folder F.12)
      - Memos to Administration, 1969-1972 (Box 188, Folder F.13)
      - Class Assignments--Congressional Elections, 1969-1972 (Box 188, Folder F.14)
      - CV and Teacher's Record, 1973 (Box 188, Folder F.15)
      - Alumni Club--Notes, 1987-1983 (Box 188, Folder F.16)
      - Opening Day Remarks, 1988 September 6 (Box 188, Folder F.17)
      - Correspondence, 1990-2002 (Box 189, Folder F.1)
      - Lecture Notes, 1992-1993, (3 Folders) (Box 189, Folder F.2-4)
      - Student Evaluations, 1971 (Box 189, Folder F.5)
        [restricted until 2051]
      - Syllabi for Courses and Seminars (Box 189)
      - "Broadcast Journalism and the Making of Public Opinion," undated (Box 189, Folder F.6)
      - "Confrontation and the Media: World Outside and the Pictures in Our Heads," 1978 Spring (Box 189, Folder F.7)
      - "The Constitution, the Public and the Media," 1984 Spring (Box 189, Folder F.8)
      - "Constitutional Law and Journalism," 1984 Spring (Box 189, Folder F.9)
      - "The Constitution, That Delicate Balance," 1983 Spring (Box 189, Folder F.10)
      - "Contemporary Civilization: Journalism for Poets, Protestors and Physicists," 1971 Spring (Box 189, Folder F.11)
      - "Contemporary Communications,"1977 Spring, (2 Folders) (Box 189, Folder F.12-13)
      - Georgene Dreishpoon lecture, 1977 Spring (Box 189, Folder F.14)
      - "Ethics in America," 1989 Spring (Box 189, Folder F.15)
      - "Five Years: 1949-1954" (Proposed), undated (Box 189, Folder F.16)
      - "The First Amendment and Electronic Journalism," 1971 (Box 189, Folder F.17)
      - "Journalism and the First Amendment," 1973 Fall (Box 189, Folder F.18)
      - "Journalism and the Law," 1978 Fall (Box 189, Folder F.19)
      - "Journalism, Law and Society," 1980 Fall (Box 189, Folder F.20)
      - "Media and Society: The Making of a Journalist," undated (Box 190, Folder F.1)
      - "The Media and the First Amendment," 1979 Fall (Box 190, Folder F.2)
      - "Media, Law, and Society," 1981 Fall (Box 190, Folder F.3)
      - "News and the Law," 1970 Spring (Box 190, Folder F.4)
      - "The Presidency," 1984 (Box 190, Folder F.5)
      - "Televison," 1970 Spring (Box 190, Folder F.6)
    - Michele Clark Fellowship Program for Minority Journalists
      - Budget and Funding Information, 1968-1975 (Box 190, Folder F.7)
      - Memos and Correspondence, 1968-1975 (Box 190, Folder F.8)
      - Press Releases, 1968-1975 (Box 190, Folder F.9)
      - Reports on Program Success, 1968-1975 (Box 190, Folder F.10)
      - Student Lists and Guidebooks, 1968-1975 (Box 190, Folder F.11)
      - Teaching Material and Course Schedules, 1968-1975 (Box 190, Folder F.12)
      - Program Brochures, 1969-1970 (Box 190, Folder F.13)
      - Program Booklet, 1969 (Box 216, Folder F.5)
      - Proposal, 1970 (Box 191, Folder F.1)
      - Teaching Curriculum, 1970-1972 (Box 191, Folder F.2)
      - Clippings--Minority Groups and Journalism, 1970-1971 (Box 191, Folder F.3)
      - Michelle Clark Memorial Service--Program and Clippings, 1972 December (Box 191, Folder F.4)
      - Graduation Speech, 1974 August 16 (Box 191, Folder F.5)
      - Student Papers (Box 191)
      - "51st State" by Diana Huffman, 1972 (Box 217, Folder F.1)
      - "The Agnew Affair" by Terrence L. Martin, 1970 (Box 217, Folder F.2)
      - "Anatomy of an Informer" by David Ball, 1973 (Box 217, Folder F.3)
      - "Anatomy of a Murder? Anatomy of a News Story" by Joan Page Nassivera, 1976 (Box 217, Folder f.4)
      - "Biography of a License: The Fifty-Year History of a Commercial Broadcast Station" by Ralph J. Begleiter, 1972 (Box 217, Folder f.5)
      - "'Black Journal' and 'Like it Is': A Discussion" by Jill N. Beasley, 1971 (Box 217, Folder f.6)
      - "Broadway's Puzzler" by Don Scott, 1973 (Box 217, Folder F.7)
      - "Crisis in Adoption Land" by Steve Petrou, 1972 (Box 217, Folder f.8)
      - "Direct Satellite Broadcasting: Implications for Telecommunications Policy" by Janine Ann Petit, 1972 (Box 217, Folder f.9)
      - "The Era of the Blacklist" by David Powell, 1975 (Box 217, Folder f.10)
      - "Faraday Wood, A Dream Deferred" by Gerthie Hartley, 1971 (Box 217, Folder f.11)
      - "Fair Game: CBS and 'The Guns of Autumn'" by Robert Engelman, 1976 (Box 217, Folder f.12)
      - "The First Amendment Goes to Court" by Leonard M. Apcar, 1976 (Box 218, Folder F.1)
      - "The First Amendment Takes a Beating in Indianapolis" by Rory Quirk, 1972 (Box 218, Folder F.2)
      - "Football at Columbia, 1870-1976" by Gregory C. Roberts, 1976 (Box 218, Folder f.3)
      - "The Gramercy Gym: Home of Champions" by Greg Aiello, 1976 (Box 218, Folder f.4)
      - "In Search of the Gullible: The Media and Their Reports on the Paranormal" by Andrew Skolnick, 1981 (Box 218, Folder F.5)
      - "Joseph P. Little: Attica Veteran" by Karen G. Gray, 1973 (Box 218, Folder f.6)
      - "Letters to the Anchorman: Talking Back to TV" by Eileen McNamara, 1976 (Box 218, Folder F.7)
      - "The Living Room Candidate: Who will Reform Broadcast Campaign Advertising?" by Betsy Bowman, 1972 (Box 218, Folder f.8)
      - "A New Breed if Black Inmate" by Karen G. Gray, 1973 (Box 218, Folder f.9)
      - "No Joy in Meadville? Nightly Cable is at the Bat" by Jeffrey Hatch, 1971 (Box 218, Folder f.10)
      - "A Study of 'How 'Rational' Men Make Decisions" by Lauren Katzowitz, 1971 (Box 218, Folder f.11)
      - "The Pay Cable Issue" by Wayne Kabak, 1975 (Box 218, Folder f.12)
      - "Portrait of a Nursing Home Patient" by Patricia Roberts, 1973 (Box 218, Folder f.13)
      - "Prescription Promotion: Selling the Doctor Drugs" by Peter Frishauf, 1972 (Box 218, Folder F.14)
      - "The Presidential Press Conference" by Diana Crawford, 1971 (Box 219, Folder F.1)
      - "Press Coverage of the Cornell Crisis: 1969 by Jaipal S. Jhala, undated (Box 219, Folder F.2)
      - "A Primer on the Fuentes Affair" by Peter Niles Baylor, 1973 (Box 219, Folder F.3)
      - "A Radio Documentary Manual" by Michael J. Strauss, 1976 (Box 219, Folder F.4)
      - "Report of the Montauk Meeting" by Stephen White, 1982 (Box 219, Folder F.5)
      - "Six Views of Times Square" by Lee McEachern, 1973 (Box 219, Folder F.6)
      - "The Soul of William Buckley" by Richard A. Reingold, 1971 (Box 219, Folder F.7)
      - "The Tale of the Tudor City: How a City Protects Itself" by Sarah R. Bedell, 1973 (Box 219, Folder F.8)
      - "Three Nights in Midtown North, or, How Would You Like to Carry a Badge and Work in Times Square?" by Marek Lewanda, 1973 (Box 219, Folder F.9)
      - "TV or Not TV? The Question of Cameras in Congress" by Don S. Dickson, 1970 (Box 219, Folder f.10)
      - "Up Against the American Flag: Artistic License vs. the New York Flag Desecration Law" by David Pitt, 1971 (Box 219, Folder f.11)
      - "Welfare in Suburbia" by Andrew J. Schorr, 1972 (Box 219, Folder F.12)
      - "What Ever Happened to Newsman's Privilege?" by Joseph Seldner, 1976 (Box 220, Folder F.1)
      - Short Student Papers, 1976-1985, (5 Folders) (Box 220, Folder F.2-6)
  - Subseries VI.4: Personal, 1934-2004
    This small subseries contains Friendly's high school transcripts and documents from his service in the Army during World War II. One letter to his mother describes the liberation of the Maulthausen concentration camp. The subseries also includes interviews with Friendly about his work at CBS and Columbia, clippings about his life and career, and obituaries and reactions to his death. Items are arranged chronologically.
    - High School Transcripts, 1934 (Box 191, Folder F.6)
    - World War II
      - Articles for India-Burma Theater Roundup, 1945 (Box 191, Folder F.7)
      - Letter, Friendly to Therese Wachenheimer, 1945 May (Box 191, Folder F.8)
      - Army Notices, 1941-1945 (Box 191, Folder F.9)
      - Memorabilia, 1941-1945 (Box 191, Folder F.10)
      - Ex-CBI Roundup Articles, 1954-1960 (Box 191, Folder F.11)
      - General, 1960s (Box 191, Folder F.12)
    - Interview by Eric Barnouw, 1968 December 27 (Box 192, Folder F.1)
    - Interview by 20/20 1981 April 25 (Box 192, Folder F.2)
    - Interview, 1995 October 20 (Box 192, Folder F.3)
    - White vs. Pennsylvania Association of Broadcasters, 1992, (2 Folders) (Box 192, Folder F.4-5)
    - Memorial Articles and Obituaries, 1998, (2 Folders) (Box 192, Folder F.6-7)
    - Clippings and Articles about Friendly
      - Biographies, 1963-1992 (Box 192, Folder F.8)
      - CBS, 1961-1962 (Box 193, Folder F.1)
      - Resignation from CBS, 1966 (Box 193, Folder F.2)
      - General, 1940-1979, (6 Folders) (Box 193, Folder F.3-8)
      - General, 1980-2004, (7 Folders) (Box 194, Folder F.1-7)
  - Subseries VI.5: Professional Activities, 1963-1989
    Friendly served on several boards outside of his usual work, four of which are represented here. In 1968, New York City mayor John Lindsay appointed Friendly as chairman of the Mayor’s Advisory Task Force on CATV and Telecommunications, which researched the feasability of introducing a city-wide cable television system to New York, and its possible impact on local television stations. Research notes, articles, correspondence, and reports document the process. Also present are memos and board proposals relating to the 1986 revision of the New York City Charter, and reports and memos from Friendly's time as a Communications advisor for the Ford Foundation. Finally, there is a small amount of correspondence and notes related to Friendly's position on the board of Riverdale County School in the Bronx.
    - Mayor's Advisory Task Force on CATV and Telecommunications (Box 195)
      - "An Economic Analysis of Community Antenna Television Systems and the Television Broadcasting Industry" by Martin H. Seiden, 1965 February 12 (Box 195, Folder F.1)
      - Clippings and Background Research, 1966-1971, (5 Folders) (Box 195, Folder F.2-6)
      - New York City CATV Franchises, circa 1965 (Box 195, Folder F.7)
      - Correspondence, 1967 (Box 195, Folder F.8)
      - "The Impact of CATV Competition on Local Television Stations," 1967 July 24 (Box 195, Folder F.9)
      - Meeting Notes, 1967 (Box 196, Folder F.1)
      - "A Proposal for Wired City Television," 1967 August (Box 196, Folder F.2)
      - Impact of the World Trade Center Buildings on Television Reception--Report to FCC, 1967-1968, (2 Folders) (Box 196, Folder F.3-4)
      - "A Report on Cable Television and Cable Telecommunications in New York City," 1968 September 14, (2 Folders) (Box 196, Folder F.5-6)
      - "The Present Status of CATV Program Origination Activities Ascertained by a Survey of Published and Unpublished Reports," 1968 November (Box 196, Folder F.7)
      - "The Future of Cable Television: Some Problems of Federal Regulation," 1970 January (Box 196, Folder F.8)
      - "Statement of Fred W. Friendly Before the Board of Estimate, City of New York," 1970 July 23 (Box 196, Folder F.9)
      - Notes on FCC Hearing Records, 1970-1971 (Box 196, Folder F.10)
      - "Analysis of Three Aspects of CATV"--Report, circa 1970 (Box 196, Folder F.11)
      - "Planning a New Community Antenna System"--Report, circa 1970 (Box 196, Folder F.12)
    - Ford Foundation (Box 197)
      - General, 1969-1971 (Box 197, Folder F.1)
      - Communications Satellite Controversy--Press Releases and Clippings, 1963-1966 (Box 197, Folder F.2)
      - Reports on Television and Higher Education, 1967 (Box 197, Folder F.3)
      - Proposals, 1969 (Box 197, Folder F.4)
      - Inter-office Memos, 1979 (Box 197, Folder F.5)
    - New York City Charter Revision
      - Memos, 1989 (Box 197, Folder F.6)
      - "Fred Friendly to Meet with City Students on Charter Revision," 1989 (Box 197, Folder F.7)
    - Riverdale School Board of Trustees--Memos, 1968-1970 (Box 197, Folder F.8)
  - Subseries VI.6: Research Files, 1960-1992
    This subseries holds files of research notes that are not clearly associated with specific projects. Topics include FCC's Fairness Doctrine and the Daily News Strike, among many others. Files have been arranged alphabetically by topic
    - General--Notes and Articles, 1960-1970, (14 Folders) (Box 198, Folder F.1-14)
    - Bay of Pigs, 1983 (Box 198, Folder F.15)
    - Black, Charles Jr., 1983 (Box 198, Folder F.16)
    - Cable Television, circa 1980 (Box 198, Folder F.17)
    - Daily News Strike, 1982 (Box 198, Folder F.18)
    - Federal Communications Commission (Box 199)
      - Notes and Articles, circa 1970 (Box 199, Folder F.1)
      - "The FCC as it Operates Today"--Transcript, 1971 October 13 (Box 199, Folder F.2)
      - "Anti-Trust Networks"--Transcript, 1972 April 24 (Box 199, Folder F.3)
      - Fairness Doctrine--Articles and Reports, 1971 (Box 199, Folder F.4)
    - Freedom of Speech, 1971 (Box 199, Folder F.5)
    - History Project Proposal, 1990 (Box 199, Folder F.6)
    - Interviews, 1975 (Box 199, Folder F.7)
    - New York City Housing and Zoning, 1990s (Box 199, Folder F.8)
    - Public Television, 1992 (Box 199, Folder F.9)
    - Vietnam, 1970 (Box 199, Folder F.10)
    - Watergate, 1973 (Box 199, Folder F.11)
    - Weinberger Meetings on the Military and the Press, 1985 (Box 199, Folder F.12)
    - Wise, Isaac, 1985 (Box 199, Folder F.13)
- Series VII: Photographs, 1917-1990
  This series contains photographs of Friendly, as well as images used in the production of his seminars and books. It has been arranged into three subseries based on subject.
  - Subseries VII.1: General, 1917-1990
    Photographs in this subseries represent a wide variety of Friendly's activities. Images show Friendly announcing radio programs for WEAN-Providence, teaching classes at Columbia, conversing with Walter Cronkite, and speaking at commencement ceremonies and other events. There are a few personal photos, including a shot of Friendly as a child and pictures with family and friends. Photographs taken for the book Minnesota Rag are also included. Images are prints in black and white or color and have been arranged chronologically.
    - S.H. Friendly Store, Oregon, undated (Box 200, Folder F.1)
    - Baby Photo, circa 1917 (Box 200, Folder F.2)
    - World War II Speech, circa 1944 (Box 200, Folder F.2)
    - WEAN Radio--Prints, circa 1940 (Box 200, Folder F.3)
    - NBC, circa 1947 (Box 200, Folder F.4)
    - NBC, 1980s (Box 200, Folder F.5)
    - Simauts Murder Case, circa 1970s (Box 200, Folder F.6)
    - Seminars, 1970-1980s (Box 200, Folder F.7)
    - Seminars, 1980s, (5 Folders) (Box 200, Folder F.8-12)
    - Columbia School, Chicago, 1980s (Box 200, Folder F.13)
    - Friendly, circa 1985-1992 (Box 200, Folder F.14)
    - Friendly and Walter Cronkite, circa 1980s (Box 200, Folder F.15)
    - Speeches and Family Photos, circa 1980s (Box 200, Folder F.16)
    - Caldwell Schorr, 1980s (Box 200, Folder F.17)
    - Minnesota Rag, circa 1980, (2 Folders) (Box 200, Folder F.18-19)
    - Classroom Images, circa 1980 (Box 200, Folder F.20)
    - Columbia Journalism School, circa 1986 (Box 200, Folder F.21)
    - Chicago Historical Society Speech, 1987 (Box 200, Folder F.22)
    - Publicity Portraits, 1988 (Box 200, Folder F.23)
    - Columbia Commencement Ceremony, circa 1990 (Box 200, Folder F.24)
    - People Magazine Photo Spread, circa 1990 (Box 200, Folder F.25)
  - Subseries VII.2: Media and Society Seminars, 1984-1990
    This subseries is comprised primarily of headshots of panelists and corresponding curriculum vitae. They include such notables as Ralph Nader, Geraldo Rivera, Andy Rooney, and Tom Brokaw. In addition to the headshots, there are photographs taken during round-table discussions at some of Friendly's most successful seminars, including The Constitution: That Delicate Balance and Ethics in America. Photographs are arranged alphabetically and include black and white and color prints, negatives, slides, and contact sheets
    - Headshots--Prints
      - Abelman, Robert--Ferris, Charles (Box 201)
      - Fiedler, Tom--Jones, David A. (Box 202)
      - Jones, David C.--Penticuff, Joy (Box 203)
      - Plum, Fred--Turner, Stansfield (Box 204)
      - Urbanski--Adam-Zucchino, (2 Folders) (Box 205, Folder F.1-2)
    - Candid Seminar Shots
      - Unknown Seminar, 1984 (Box 205, Folder F.3)
      - America's Schools --Prints, Slides, (4 Folders) (Box 221)
      - Business and the Media--Negatives, Prints, Slides, 1984, (2 Folders) (Box 205, Folder F.4-5)
      - The Constitution: That Delicate Balance --Contact Sheets, Prints, 1983 (Box 205, Folder F.6)
      - The Constitution: That Delicate Balance --Contact Sheets, Prints, Slides, 1983, (3 Folders) (Box 206, Folder F.1-3)
      - Constitutional Bicentennial--Prints, 1984 October 1 (Box 206, Folder F.4)
      - Ethics in America --Prints, Slides, circa 1989, (3 Folders) (Box 206, Folder F.5-7)
      - Ethics in America --Prints, Slides, circa 1989, (4 Folders) (Box 221)
      - Ethics and Marketing--Prints, 1986 October (Box 206, Folder F.8)
      - Hospitals and the Elderly: An Alliance of Quality --Prints, 1987 March (Box 206, Folder F.9)
      - Unknown Seminar, 1984 (Box 207, Folder F.1)
      - Managing our Miracles --Contact Sheets, Negatives, Prints, 1986, (2 Folders) (Box 207, Folder F.2-3)
      - Media, Power, and Democracy --Prints, 1987 (Box 207, Folder F.4)
      - The Other Side of the News --Color Slides, Prints, circa 1990, (4 Folders) (Box 207, Folder F.5-8)
      - The Presidency and the Constitution --Prints, Slides, 1987 (Box 208, Folder F.1)
      - Presidents Carter and Ford at Congress Hall, Philadelphia--Contact Sheets, Prints, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 208, Folder F.2-3)
      - Terrorism--Contact Sheets, Prints, Slides, 1987, (3 Folders) (Box 208, Folder F.4-6)
  - Subseries VII.3: CBS--Prints, 1951-1965
    Photographs taken during Friendly's time at CBS are housed in this subseries. Most shots show Friendly speaking with notable program guests such as Dwight D. Eisenhower, Edward R. Murrow, Lyndon B. Johnson, John F. Kennedy, and Carl Sandberg, and some include the set and cameramen in the background. All items are prints or contact sheets and have been arranged alphabetically by subject. Oversize photos have been housed separately.
    - Group: John Kennedy, Linden B. Johnson, Edward Murrow, Eisenhower, 1950s (Box 208, Folder F.7)
    - Group: Carl Sandberg, Edward Murrow, Louis Armstrong, 1950s (Box 208, Folder F.8)
    - Danny Kaye Party, circa 1957 (Box 209)
    - Taft, Robert, 1951 November 25 (Box 209, Folder F.3)
    - Talbott, Refect, undated (Box 209, Folder F.4)
    - Texas Drought, 1953 October 13 (Box 209, Folder F.5)
    - Textile Slump, 1954 February 2 (Box 209, Folder F.6)
    - Tito, Marshall, 1957 June 30 (Box 209, Folder F.7)
    - Toynbee, Arnold J., 1953 January 25 (Box 209, Folder F.8)
    - Trieste, 1953 November 10 (Box 209, Folder F.9)
    - Truman and Film Crew, 1958 February 2 (Box 209, Folder F.10)
    - U Nu, 1955 March 15 (Box 209, Folder F.11)
    - Veterans of Foreign Wars, 1954 February 2 (Box 209, Folder F.12)
    - Walter, Francis, 1955 March 8 (Box 209, Folder F.13)
    - Warren Earl, 1953 May 10 (Box 209, Folder F.14)
    - West, Rebecca, 1955 March 22 (Box 209, Folder F.15)
    - Wong, H.K., undated (Box 209, Folder F.16)
    - Friendly, Eisenhower, Walter Cronkite, undated (Box 216, Folder F.1)
    - Friendly and John Kennedy, 1960s (Box 216, Folder F.2)
    - Friendly and Lyndon B. Johnson, circa 1960s (Box 216, Folder F.3)
    - Columbia Classroom, undated (Box 216, Folder F.4)
- Series VIII: Media, 1961-1991
  Series VIII holds audio-visual material, including recordings of Media and Society seminars, episodes from several news programs, and television specials featuring Friendly. Formats include VHS tapes, Umatic tapes, 7- and 5-inch audio tapes, audiocassettes, mini cassettes, records, and diskettes. Items have been arranged by format and title.
  - Floppy Disks (Box 210)
    - "Mass Media and the Government"--Transcripts, 1991 October 4, (8 inch) (Box 210)
    - Drugs in America, 1989, (5.25 inch) (Box 210)
    - The Other Side of the News, 1988, (5.25 inch) (Box 210)
    - Untitled--Floppy Disk, undated, (7 disks; (5.25 inch) (Box 210)
  - Audio Reels
    - Dinner Honoring Friendly, Imperial Ballroom Center, 1975 January 28, (7 inch) (Box 210)
    - Gordon Glister Sheriffs Conference, 1975 October 19, (5 inch) (Box 210)
    - KNXN News Radio, undated, (7 inch) (Box 210)
    - "News and the Law"--Helene Schwartz, 1973 January 22, (7 inch) (Box 210)
    - "Pentagon Papers," 1973 May 11, (7 inch) (Box 210)
    - "Watergate and the Media," 1973 October 29, (7 inch); (2 reels) (Box 210)
    - WNYC Book and Author Luncheon, 1967 April 17, (7 inch) (Box 210)
  - Audio Cassettes (Box 211)
    - Untitled--Micro Cassette, undated (Box 211)
    - Untitled, undated (Box 211)
    - Friendly Debriefing, 1975 February 15 (Box 211)
    - Judge Hugh Stuart, 1976 July 10 (Box 211)
    - In the Face of Terrorism, Panel III: "Violence in Northern Shamrock: Terrorism or Civil War?" 1986 September 27, (6 cassettes) (Box 211)
    - "In Celebrated Company,"1987 October, (3 cassettes) (Box 211)
    - Medicine and Society, 1984 (Box 212)
      - Moderated by Arthur Miller, 1984, (6 cassettes) (Box 212)
      - Moderated by Hal Edgar, undated, (3 cassettes) (Box 212)
    - Untitled Seminar, undated
      - Moderated by Arthur Miller, undated, (6 cassettes) (Box 212)
      - Moderated by Hal Edgar, undated, (3 cassettes) (Box 212)
    - College Sports Program, 1989 July 7, (6 cassettes) (Box 213)
    - Drugs in America, Panels 1-3, 1989, (11 cassettes) (Box 213)
  - Records (Box 214)
    - "Children and God" by Tony Schwartz--LP, 1966 (Box 214)
    - "The Sound of the Family Man" by Tony Schwartz--LP, circa 1968 (Box 214)
  - 1 inch reels
    - The President and the Constitution--"The Making of a Justice," 1987 April 24, (2 reels) (Box 214)
  - Videotapes
    - "Watergate Openings and Closings", undated, (Umatic tape; 3 tapes) (Box 214)
    - "Confronting the Media: Reporters, Ethics, and Business", 1985 February 6, (VHS tape) (Box 215)
    - "A Conversation with Fred Friendly and Dallin Oaks", 1983 October, (Unatic tape) (Box 215)
    - "Experiment in Utah", 1983 December, (VHS tape) (Box 215)
    - "Free Press, Fair Trial", 1987 February 20, (VHS tape; 2 tapes) (Box 215)
    - "Intimidation and Violence: The Daily News Strike", 1990, (VHS tape) (Box 215)